Virgil M. Brand papers, 1889-1990
American Numismatic Society
- Ledgers and binders
  - Place (Pla) - coins categorized by place of origin
    - Pla 2 - mostly ca. 21000-38000
  - Ring Binders
      nnan0034/c_7fc7477fece449ae357c3992a88c567e
    - Sales Book #1, 1932-1937
    - Sales Book #2, 1937-1942
    - Consignments, 1935-1944
    - Consignments, 1945-1947 (contains 1936-1945?)
    - Consignments #2, 1936-1947
    - Consignments III, 1938-1945
    - U.S.A. Gold, Philadelphia Mint
    - U.S.A. Gold, All Mints Except "P", Charms, U.S. Territories, Swedish Plate
    - U.S. Ledger Code Book
    - Ledger, A-D (alphabetical by country/place)
    - Coin Ledger, E,F,G (alphabetical by country/place)
    - Ledger, F-Z (alphabetical by country/place)
    - J.B.A. (Jane Brand-Allen)
    - Netherlands (green ring binder)
  - Photocopies of Ledgers
      nnan0034/c_c221225d95f3ecd3c1dd05d2d9adf4fa
    - 33 binders and 10 bags containing a complete photocopied set of the Secondary Ledgers
    - 1 bag containing a photocopy of ledger Ch1
    - 1 bag containing a photocopy of ledger Ch2
    - 1 bag containing a photocopy of ledger Ex1
    - 1 bag containing a photocopy of ledger Ex2
- Other loose materials
    nnan0034/c_348af6f80093f86d808668e301cfb1e5
  - U.S. Colonial ledger
  - Hall Collection (blue binder)
  - Box of slides of Brand coins
  - Box of photographs and other items pertaining to Brand sales, 1980s
  - 26 catalogs (Sotheby's, Bowers and Merena) for sales of Brand items, 1983-1990
  - 1 box of rubber stamps used by Virgil M. Brand